A Guide to the Records of the Fairhope Industrial Association and the Fairhope Single Tax Corporation, 1893-1997
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Correspondence and Papers of Secretaries of Fairhope
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data (238) 1982-1984 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Bay Meadows subdivision (239) 1979 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Brown's (240) 1974-1985 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Calculations (241) 1977-1985 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Fairland (242) 1982-1988 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Interest (243) 1980-1983 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Land Fund (244) 1976-1984 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data - Legislative Bills (245) 1977-1979 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Rent Adjustment Comparisons (246) 1977 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Rent Determination Methods (247) 1966-1984 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Rent Determination Methods (248) 1968-1971 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Rent Determination Methods (249) 1975-1984 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Rent Determination Methods ' Coleman Recommendations (250) 1980-1982 (Folder 225-251)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation: Papers of Gale W. Rowe: Rent Study Data ' Rent Study Committee -251 1969-1984 (Folder 225-251)
- Business Papers of the Fairhope Single Tax Corporation
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Annual Reports (252) 1944-1955 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Annual Reports (253) 1956-1977 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Tax Receipts (254) 1902-1904 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers (255) 1903 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers (256) 1904 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers (257) 1905-1915 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Warrants and Tax Receipts (2 folders) (258-259) 1905 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Vouchers (2 folders) (260-261) 1906 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Warrants and Tax Receipts (2 folders) (262-263) 1907 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Warrants and Vouchers (2 folders) (264-265) 1908-1910 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Peoples Railroad Company certificates of J. A. Patterson (266) 1916-1917 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers (2 folders) (267-268) 1916-1926 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers (2 folders) (269-270) 1927 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers (271) 1928 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-E (272) 1926-1928 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F (273) 1926-1928 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Fairhope Coal & Supply Company (274) 1926-1928 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: G-L (275) 1926-1928 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: M-Q (276) 1926-1928 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: R-Z (277) 1926-1928 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Monroe Smith and C. S. Eggleston (278) 1926-1928 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Treasurer's Reports (279) 1925-1928 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Receipts (2 folders) (280-281) 1928-1929 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers (282) 1929 (Folder 252-282)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-F (283) 1930-1931 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Fairhope Coal & Supply Company (284) 1930-1931 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: G-L (285) 1930-1931 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: M (286) 1930-1931 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: N-R (287) 1930-1931 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: J. A. Patterson (288) 1930-1931 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: S-Z (289) 1930-1931 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Marion Smith (290) 1930-1931 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-O (291) 1932-1935 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: P-R (292) 1932-1933 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: S-Z (293) 1932-1933 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-F (294) 1934-1935 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: G-K (295) 1934-1935 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: L-M (296) 1934-1935 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: N-R (297) 1934-1935 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: S (298) 1934-1935 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Southern Bell Telephone (299) 1930-1947 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: T-Z (300) 1934-1935 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-E (301) 1935-1936 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F-K (302) 1936 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: L-S (303) 1936 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: T-Z (304) 1936 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Tax Receipts (305) 1936 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-E (306) 1937-1940 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F (307) 1937-1940 (Folder 283-307)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: G-K (308) 1937-1940 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: L-P (309) 1937-1940 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: R-Z (310) 1937-1940 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Marion Smith (311) 1937-1940 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Tax Receipts (312) 1938 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Tax Receipts (2 folders) (313-314) 1939 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Tax Receipts (2 folders) (315-316) 1940 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-E (317) 1940-1949 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F-G (318) 1940-1949 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: H-L (319) 1941-1949 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: M-S (320) 1941-1949 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Southern Bell (321) 1940-1947 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: T-Z (322) 1941-1949 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Receipts A-K (323) 1948-1949 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Receipts L-Z (324) 1948-1949 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-B (325) 1950-1959 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: C (326) 1950-1959 (Folder 308-326)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: D-E (327) 1950-1959 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F (328) 1950-1959 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: G-J (329) 1950-1959 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: L-N (330) 1950-1959 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: O-R (331) 1950-1959 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: S (332) 1950-1959 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: T-Z (333) 1950-1959 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A (334) 1960-1967 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: B-C (335) 1960-1967 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Cemetery Trust Fund (336) 1961-1965 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Cemetery Trust Fund (337) 1966-1967 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: D-I (338) 1960-1967 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Fairhope Courier (339) 1960-1967 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: L-O (340) 1960-1967 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: P-Z (341) 1960-1967 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-C (342) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Abstracts (343) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: D-E (344) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F-G (345) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Fairhope Courier (346) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: H-M (347) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: N-O (348) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: P-Q (349) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: R (350) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: S-Z (351) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Shepherd Printing (352) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Southern Central Bell (353) 1968-1973 (Folder 327-353)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-B (354) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: C (355) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: D (356) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: E (357) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F-H (358) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Fairhope Title & Survey Company, Inc. (359) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: I-L (360) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: M (361) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: N-O (362) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: P (363) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: R, T-Z (364) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: S (365) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: South Central Bell (366) 1974-1978 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-C (367) 1979-1980 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: D-F (368) 1979-1980 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: G-J (369) 1979-1980 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: K-O (370) 1979-1980 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: P-S (371) 1979-1980 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: T-Z (372) 1979-1980 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-B (373) 1981-1984 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: C (374) 1981-1984 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: D-E (375) 1981-1984 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F-K (376) 1981-1984 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: L-O (377) 1981-1984 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: P-R (378) 1981-1984 (Folder 354-378)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: S-Z (379) 1981-1984 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: South Central Bell (380) 1981-1984 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-B (381) 1985-1989 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: C (382) 1985-1989 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: D-E (383) 1985-1989 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F-J (384) 1985-1989 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: K-O (385) 1985-1989 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: P (386) 1985-1989 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Pen & Ink (387) 1985-1989 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: R-Z (388) 1985-1989 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: South Central Bell (389) 1985-1989 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: A-B (390) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: C (391) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: D (392) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: E (393) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: F-G (394) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: H (395) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: I-N (396) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: O (397) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: P-R (398) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: Pen & Ink (399) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: S-Z (400) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Papers: South Central Bell (2 folders) (401-402) 1990-1993 (Folder 379-402)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Voucher Book (403) 1895 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Capital Stock Certificates (404) 1895-1905 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Members Information (405) 1895-1932 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Treasurer's Account Book (406) 1897-1904 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Monthly Statements (407) 1903-1907 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Receipt Book for Land Rent (408) 1904, 1908 Dec-1909 Jan (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Day Book Index (409) 1904-1905 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Board of Directors Records (410) 1904-1910 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Water Rent and Taxes (411) 1906-1912 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Rent Roll (412) 1907-1909 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Grants, Transfers, Surrenders and Forfeitures (413) 1907-1917 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Monthly Statements (414) 1907-1918 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Day Book and Journal (415) 1908-1909 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Resource Ledger (416) 1908-1909 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Wharf Company Cash Book (417) 1908-1914 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Rent Roll (418) 1910-1912 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Wharf Company Minutes and Reports (419) 1910-1915 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Bank Account Book (420) 1911-1912 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Survey Notes re Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Land (421) 1912-1914 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Bank Account Book (422) 1915-1918 (Folder 403-422)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Rent Accounts (423) 1916-1919 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Cash Book; "Real Personal Totals" and "Country Lands" (424) 1918-1919; 1927 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Telephone Ledger (425) 1920-1922 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Bank Account Book (426) 1921-1923 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Rent Receipts (427) 1923-1924 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Monthly Statements (428) 1924-1927 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Estate of Henry Crawford (429) 1930-1931 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Bank Account Book (430) 1931-1943 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Estate of Ernest B. Gaston (431) 1934-1955 (Folder 423-445)
  - 1965-1967
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Trust Account of Ernest B. Gaston (432) 1936-1937 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Estate of Ernest B. Gaston (433) 1938-1967 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Expenses (434) 1941-1942 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Journal (435) 1941-1944 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Sundries (436) 1943 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Pertinent Data/City of Fairhope, and Fairhope Single Tax Corporation ' 1948 to date (437) 1948- (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: History/City of Fairhope, Engineer Data, Section (loose leaf notebook removed from Pertinent Data...) (438) 1948- (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Excess Taxes Receipt Books (439) 1966-1970 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Books Accounts (440) 1968-1974 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Excess Taxes Receipt Books (441) 1970-1975 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Book Sales Receipts (442) 1973-1980 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Tax Book (443) 1975 (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Engineers Level Book (444) n.d. (Folder 423-445)
  - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Business Volumes: Tax Certificate Book (445) n.d. (Folder 423-445)
- Oversize Bound Volumes-Separate from boxes
  - Business Volumes:
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Receipts (Volume 1) 1904 Jan-1909 May
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 2) 1905 Oct-1910 Jan
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 3) 1910 Jan-1912 Jun
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 4) 1912 Jul-1914 May
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 5) 1914 May-1917 Jan
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 6) 1917 Jan-1918 Dec
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 7) 1919 Jan-1920 Dec
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 8) 1920 Dec-1924 Oct
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 9) 1924 Oct-1927 Apr
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 10) 1927 May-1929 Jul
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 11) 1929 Aug-1931 Oct
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 12) 1931 Nov-1934 May
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 13) 1934 Jun-1936 Dec
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 14) 1937 Jan-1939 Feb
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 15) 1939 Mar-1941 Mar
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 16) 1941 Apr-1943 Jan
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 17) 1943 Jan-1944 Jul
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 18) 1944 Jul-1946 Jul
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 19) 1946 Aug-1948 Aug
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 20) 1948 Aug-1950 Jul
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 21) 1950 Aug-1952 Aug
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 22) 1952 Sep-1954 Aug
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 23) 1954 Sep-1956 Apr
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 24) 1956 Apr-1957 Nov
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 25) 1957 Nov-1959 Apr
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 26) 1959 Apr-1960 Nov
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 27) 1960 Nov-1962 Apr
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 28 1962 Apr-1963 Nov
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 29) 1963 Nov-1965 May
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 30) 1965 Jun-1966 Nov
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 31) 1966 Dec-1968 Apr
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 32) 1968 May-1969 Oct
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 33) 1969 Nov-1971 Mar
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 34) 1971 Mar-1972 Jul
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 35) 1972 Aug-1973 Oct
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 36) 1973 Nov-1975 Jan
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 37) 1975 Feb-1977 Jan
    - Fairhope Single Tax Corporation Cash Book (Volume 38) 1977 Feb-1978 May
    - Accounts Ledger (Volume 39) ca. 1894-1896
    - Accounts Ledger (Volume 40) ca. 1904-1928
    - Accounts Ledger (Volume 41) ca. 1927-1931
    - Accounts Ledger (Volume 42) ca. 1928-1930
    - Accounts Ledger (Volume 43) ca. 1932-1937
    - Accounts Ledger (Volume 44) ca. 1938-1946
    - Bank of Fairhope checkbook (Volume 45) 1937 Apr-1940 Feb
    - Rent Accounts (Volume 46) 1912 Jan-1916 Jul
    - (Volume 47) 1914-1918 Rent Accounts
    - Rent Accounts (Volume 48) 1919 Jul-1923 Jul
    - Rent Accounts (Volume 49) 1923 Jul-1927 Jul
    - Scrapbooks of newspaper clippings (Volume 50) ca. 1894-1913
    - Membership Certificates (#1-293) (Volume 51) 1905-1980
  - Minutes
    - Fairhope Industrial Association Executive Council Minutes (Volume 52) 1896 Jun-1899 Jan